module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What rapper often wears a large clock necklace during his performances?', 
    a: 'Flavor Flav',
    b: 'Chuck D',
    c: 'Ice Cube',
    d: '50 Cent',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where does the Euphrates River flow through?', 
    a: 'Iraq',
    b: 'Romania',
    c: 'Yemen',
    d: 'Egypt',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: '"Betcha can\'t eat just one." was the slogan for what snack?', 
    a: 'Fritos',
    b: 'Lay\'s Potato Chips',
    c: 'Wheat Thins',
    d: 'Ritz Crackers',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which poet wrote the famous poem "For Whom The Bell Tolls"?',
    a: 'Lars Ulrich',
    b: 'William Shakespeare',
    c: 'John Donne',
    d: 'Emily Dickinson',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: '"Enokitake" is a type of what?', 
    a: 'Mushroom',
    b: 'Fish',
    c: 'Tree',
    d: 'Pear',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which airline merged with United in 2012?', 
    a: 'US Airways',
    b: 'AirTran',
    c: 'Northwest',
    d: 'Continental',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What two-handed weapon combined a spear and battle-axe?', 
    a: 'Morning Star',
    b: 'Halberd',
    c: 'Pike',
    d: 'Ulfberht',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these ingredients is NOT used in baklava?', 
    a: 'Honey',
    b: 'Chocolate',
    c: 'Phyllo Dough',
    d: 'Nuts',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which hat is usually red and shaped like a truncated cone?', 
    a: 'Fez',
    b: 'Beret',
    c: 'Boater',
    d: 'Montera',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: '"Hoggle" is a fictional character from what movie?',
    a: 'Lord of the Rings',
    b: 'Harry Potter',
    c: 'Labyrinth',
    d: 'The Neverending Story',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];
